In the twilight's gentle glow,
Where dreams and hopes doth flow,
I'll weave a tapestry of words,
A poem to touch your soul's chords.
In fields of golden sunlight gleaming,
Where love and beauty lie, dreaming,
I'll pluck the stars from the night's embrace,
And sprinkle them upon your grace.
With verses crafted like petals of a rose,
I'll paint a portrait only your heart knows,
Each line a whisper, soft and true,
A melody that sings of me and you.
Let me sketch the moon's silver smile,
And capture it within each verse's mile,
Let my words dance on the river's flow,
And carry your spirit where dreams may go.
Through meadows blooming with fragrant delight,
I'll trace your dreams in the soft moonlight,
And in the tapestry of my poetic art,
I'll etch the love that binds our hearts.
For in these lines, a love story unfolds,
A tale of passion that forever holds,
In every stanza, a love letter to you,
A masterpiece painted in words so true.
So let this poem be a sweet caress,
A sanctuary where your heart finds rest,
And may it remind you, forevermore,
That in my words, your love I adore.